ffxivclock.com 2019-05-29

# FFXIV Clock - Privacy Policy

    This privacy policy discloses the privacy practices for FFXIVClock.com. This privacy policy applies solely to information collected by this web site. 
    It will notify you of the following:
       • What personally identifiable information is collected from you through the web site.
       • How identifiable information it is used and with whom it may be shared.
       • What choices are available to you regarding the use of your data.
       • The security procedures in place to protect the misuse of your information.
       • How you can correct any inaccuracies in the information.
    
    FFXIVClock.com uses Google Analytics to track data about our visitors. 
    Google Analytics records the following:
       • What website refred you to us
       • Your session duration
       • What kind of device and browser you are using
       • General geo location and other demographics information
       • What pages and actions you perform while in our domain
       
    The tracking information allows us to analyze what content is best served for our visitors - what pages are most interested and what features are used the most. With this we can better prioritize our work and make better design decisions.
    
    The following Google Analytics features have been implemented:
       • Remarketing with Google Analytics
       • Google Display Network Impression Reporting
       • Google Analytics Demographics and Interest Reporting
       • Integrated services that require Google Analytics to collect data via advertising cookies and anonymous identifiers
    
    Using the [Ads Settings](https://www.google.com/settings/ads), users can opt-out of Google Analytics for Display Advertising and customize Google Display Network ads. 
    
    For more information and steps on outping out, please visit the [ Google Analytics' currently available opt-outs ](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout/) page.
    
    All of FFXIV Clock activity falls within the bounds of the Google Analytics Terms of Service.
    
    We are a participant in the Amazon Services LLC Associates Program, an affiliate advertising program designed to provide a means for us to earn fees by linking to Amazon.com and affiliated sites.

    We are the sole owners of the information collected on this site. We have access to/collect information that you voluntarily give us via email or other direct contact from you. We will not sell or rent this information to anyone.
    
    We will use your information to respond to you, regarding the reason you contacted us. We will not share your information with any third party outside of our organization, other than as necessary to fulfill your request, e.g. to ship an order.
    
    We will collect/store information about site usage, eg: What items users select on the website and how often. User IPs are automatically recorded in the server Apache logs, and we may store user's IP in regards to their usage of the site.

    You may opt out of any future contacts from us at any time. You can do the following at any time by contacting us via the email address or contact us form given on our website:
       • See what data we have about you, if any.
       • Change/correct any data we have about you.
       • Have us delete any data we have about you.
       • Express any concern you have about our use of your data.

    We do not collect sensitive information (besides IP Address), except what you voluntarily submit via the contact us page or via email. This information will not be shared or sold. It will only be used to help resolve any issues you are having with our service by the site owners and staff. It will be stored in our gmail account, with all of the securities present in gmail. We will not share or sell access to this email account with anybody outside of FFXIVClock.

    Our Privacy Policy may change from time to time and all updates will be posted on this page.
    
    If you feel that we are not abiding by this privacy policy, you should contact us immediately via email (ffxivclock at gmail).
